1. comment("Story: Login to CURA system")
5. comment("Given that the user has the valid login information")
9. openBrowser(G_SiteURL)
13. click(findTestObject("Page_CuraHomepage/btn_MakeAppointment"))
17. setText(findTestObject("Page_Login/txt_UserName"), Username)
21. setText(findTestObject("Page_Login/txt_Password"), Password)
25. comment("When he logins to CURA system")
29. click(findTestObject("Page_Login/btn_Login"))
33. comment("Then he should be able to login successfully")
37. landingPage = verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("Page_CuraAppointment/div_Appointment"), G_Timeout)
41. closeBrowser()
1. testCaseName = testCaseContext.getTestCaseId()
5. if (testCaseName.contains("Skip"))
1. openBrowser("http://demoaut.katalon.com")